

CV

Troels Byskov Åhusene 3, 1, 4 8000 Aarhus C (+45) 22 44 17 58 | troelsbyskov@outlook.com www.troelsbyskov.tk/en/ LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/troelsbyskov/en

TROELS BYSKOV

INTRODUCTION

DEDICATED MEDIA STUDENT READY FOR CHALLENGES

I have always been very analytical which made media studies the right choice for me. Here I have built a strong knowledge of and experience with quantitative as well as qualitative user surveys and analyses – both online and offline. I am, furthermore, a strong communicator and have built a big knowledge of business communication through my minor in international communication. I am, therefore, both strong analytically and able to create an overview of big user surveys as well as being great at communicating this knowledge – both in speech and writing.

My academic and theoretical foundation is supported by a great practical experience from my jobs where clear communication – both between colleagues and to customers – have been of big importance. Additionally, I have a self-imposed interest in learning more by attending various courses and through the construction of my own web page.

EDUCATION

STUDY ABROAD, REGENT'S UNIVERSITY LONDON



15.01.2018 - present

- Through this study abroad, I have strengthened my competencies within marketing and public relations.
- I have, furthermore, become at home in the English language after half a year in which all teaching and social events have been conducted in English.

BA IN MEDIA STUDIES, AARHUS UNIVERSITET

Minor in International Communication



2015 - present

- At media studies I have built a strong analytical faculty regarding companies' problems and which possibilities the media gives. I am well versed in Gallup's analytical tools.
- I have written my bachelor project about podcast firms' positioning in the society and which media law that is relevant to these firms. The project had a focus on the firm Mediano. I received the best grade for my bachelor project.

EDUCATION

FOLK HIGH SCHOOL ABROAD, HÖJSKOLENDK



(continued)

05.07.2016 - 05.08.2016

- I was at a folk high school abroad at The US Virgin Islands.
- I build up competencies within project management and teambuilding and I obtained a greater cultural understanding through volunteer work during the stay.

DANISH STX (HIGH SCHOOL), HOLSTEBRO GYMNASIUM OG HF



- 2011 2014
 - Social studies programme with the subjects social studies, Danish, English, history and mathematics at A-level.
 - I was chosen to and participated in a Masterclass course in English.

CONTINUATION SCHOOL, LOMBORG GYMNASTIK- OG IDRÆTSEFTERSKOLE

2010 - 2011



WORK EXPERIENCE

SALESPERSON, ELGIGANTEN, HOLSTEBRO, VIBY OG AARHUS C

01.06.2014 - 15.11.2017



Through my job at Elgiganten I have learned to provide great customer service even in stressed situations and with many balls in the air. This has been reinforced through my participation in Elgiganten's internal sales training course Cat 2.

SALESPERSON, FONA, AARHUS C

FONA

01.08.2015 - 31.03.2016

WAITER, BONE'S RESTAURANTS, HOLSTEBRO

01.03.2013 - 31.05.2015



 To work at a restaurant has taught me to keep a cool head and to keep an overview of the situation when things move quickly.

CHOSEN COURSES

LEARN DIGITAL, GOOGLE, ONLINE

An online course about the entire Google marketing universe.

Certified on 20.03.2017

SUCCES ONLINE, GOOGLE, AARHUS

A three-part course about Google's marketing platforms with a special focus on Google AdWords.

08.02.2017 - 02.03.2017

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP CC, CA A-KASSE, AARHUS

A three hours introduction course to Adobe Photoshop CC. 01.12.2016

IT COMPETENCIES

GALLUP'S ANALYTICAL TOOLS

 Through my education I have been trained in Gallup's analytical tools, including both The Viewer Survey and Danish Online Index (Instar Analytics), and Index Denmark/Gallup (GallupPC).

ONLINE MARKETING

 I am self-taught in various online marketing tools. I am familiar with Google Analytics, AdWords and Tag Manager as well as Facebook's marketing tools and Pixel.

THE OFFICE SUITE

 I master both Word, Excel and PowerPoint (and similar office programs) at a professional level.

LANGUAGES

DANISH

Danish is my native language and I speak it fluently.

ENGLISH

I speak English on a professional level.

GERMAN

I speak German at a conversational level.

PERSONAL AND LEISURE ACTIVITIES

PERSONAL

I am born and raised in Holstebro in the western Jutland. I moved to Aarhus in the summer of 2015 to study. Since then I have lived in London for six months in connection with my study abroad period.

LEISURE ACTIVITIES

I have a lot of different interest in my free time. I spend a lot of time being social with my friends and family and, furthermore, I stay active by weight-lifting, jogging and mountain biking. Before moving to Aarhus, I was rowing at a high level.

FURTHER INFORMATION

REFERENCES

References from employers can be obtained if interested.

CONTACT ME ON E-MAIL

troelsbyskov@outlook.com

CONTACT ME ON THE PHONE

(+45) 22 44 17 58

VISIT MY WEBSITE

www.troelsbyskov.tk/en/